Maxwell Dunn

(858) 775-7469 ♦ max.dunn63@gmail.com ♦ GitHub: https://github.com/maxd66

LinkedIn:https://www.linkedin.com/in/maxwell-dunn-a30374188/

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Science: Neuroscience And Physiology, June 2021 **The University of California - San Diego -** La Jolla, CA

Full-Stack Flex Engineer Course Completion: MERN Stack, August 2021 The University of California - San Diego Extension - La Jolla, CA

High School Diploma: 2017

Mission Hills High School - San Marcos, CA

- HTML/CSS
- JavaScript/Jquery
- AJAX
- Node.js
- MySQL
- Endless work ethic
- Critical Thinking

SKILLS

- Problem-Solving
- Fast learner
- Leadership abilities
- Thrives in a team
- Detail-oriented
- Punctual

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

I am an extremely motivated, hard worker, and I strive to go the extra mile. I have years of leadership experience, but am completely able to work as a unit with any team of people. Whether it's programming, education, or medicine, all of my work and study has been dedicated to achieving a career where I can work with and aid people of all ages and with any variety of grievances. In all of my professional experiences, I have been able to learn quickly, adapt to and overcome the challenges I face, and excel beyond expectations.

WORK HISTORY

Manager and Mathematics Instructor, 06/2018 to Present

Mathnasium – San Marcos, CA

- Coordinate instructors and students to ensure efficient learning, and proper share of work among the team.
- Train new staff, acknowledge achievements and outstanding performance, and reprimand discouraged behavior and unprofessional actions.
- Think critically, on the spot, to find the best way to teach a wide variety of mathematical techniques and skills, in a way that is fun and exciting to a variety of students.
- Interact and communicate with parents and guardians(customers/clients), i.e. answer any questions they have, and address any of their needs or concerns.
- Effectively work together with my team of instructors to ensure the best possible experience for our students.
- Manage student's learning plans, grade assessments, and update their parents/guardians on their progress.
- Work with children with learning disabilities, and/or special needs, and develop strategies to maintain their focus and cultivate a positive learning environment.
- Assist in the management of the students in the center, and the training of new instructors.

• Perform custodial duties like wiping tables, vacuuming, taking out the trash, and cleaning the bathroom to maintain a healthy environment for the staff and students.

Guest Advisor, 06/2019 to 08/2020

Gamestop – San Marcos, CA

- Provided sincere and quality customer service to patrons in-store and over the phone.
- Worked with a team of sales associates to help each other, and the store, meet their goals.
- Organized products in-store and developed marketing strategies to promote sales and better advertise our products.
- Worked with upset or confused customers to find effective solutions to their problems.
- Promoted specific items, memberships, and warranties to provide the customer with the best possible product, and generate more income for the store.

Palomar Pathmaker Intern, 06/2018 to 06/2021

Palomar Medical Center – Escondido, CA

- Assist Nurses and CNAs in providing high-quality patient care.
- Transport patients throughout the hospital for X-Rays, Transfers, Discharges, etc.
- Ambulating patients, providing Oral Care, assuming the role of a Sitter, performing In Bed Baths, setting up rooms before patient arrival, emptying Foley catheters, tying restraints, feeding patients, and managing heart monitors are only some of the duties I am responsible for.
- Handle and transport COVID and flu specimen
- Observed and assisted with several types of medical procedures.